Washington, D.C. Postcard Collection P030 P030
Stage
Washington, D.C. Postcard Collection
1848-1940
Stage
P030
7 boxes
Biographical / Historical
As common as American society considers the postcard today, it was not until the 1893 World's Columbian Exposition in Chicago that the first souvenir "post cards" were available for purchase in the United States. These cards featured illustrations of the various fair buildings printed on government-issued postal cards and privately printed souvenir cards. The government postal cards were imprinted with one-cent indicias while the privately printed souvenir cards required two-cents postage to be applied. Writing was not permitted on the address side of these cards.
Five years passed before private printers were granted, by an act of Congress on May 19, 1898, permission to print and sell post cards that bore the inscription Private Mailing Card. These cards could now be mailed at the same one-cent rate as the government issued cards.
The Federal government granted use of the word Post Card to private printers on December 24, 1901. Writing was still not permitted on the address side. Use of post cards with "divided backs," allowing both the address and a message on one side, was permitted on March 1, 1907. Thus marked the beginning in which millions, if not billions, of Washington, D.C. post cards have been printed and sold.
Besides depicting images of places that may no longer exist, postcards often contain messages offering documentation representative of a time and place. From observations of historic events to matters of personnel concern, insights are given into the life and times of the postcard's sender.
Custodial History
The postcards in this collection have been donated ongoing to the Washingtoniana Division since circa 1934.
Scope and Contents
The collection consists of three linear feet, consisting of about 2000 postcards and 24 postcard folders. The earliest postcards in the collection date from circa 1898. Due to Washington, D.C.'s continual focus as a tourist destination, contemporary postcards continue to be added to the collection. The greatest percentage of material dates from the 1920s to the 1940s.
The collection consists almost exclusively of imprinted (ink) postcards with less than a dozen being of the "real-photo" (gelatin silver) variety. The collection leans heavily towards images of tourist Washington but many images of "hometown" Washington are included as well (Businesses, Churches, Organizations, Restaurants, Schools – Private/Public, Stores, and Streets).
Postcards are arranged by specific subject headings. Please use the marker provided in each box to assure that postcards are returned to their proper place. Further information on deltiology, or postcard collecting, may be learned by visiting the following web sites.
Architecture; Business; Neighborhoods; Photographs
- Series 1
  - Aerial Views, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, Dept. of, undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Airports – National, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - American Red Cross, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Archives Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Arlington Cemetery, undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Army War College, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Art Galleries - Corcoran, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Art Galleries - Freer, undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Art Galleries - National, undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Art Galleries - Phillips, undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Auditoriums – Washington, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Banks – American Security and Trust Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Baseball, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Botanical Gardens, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Bridges - Arlington Memorial, undated (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Bridges - Cabin John, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Bridges - Connecticut Avenue, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Bridges - Key, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Businesses - Acacia Mutual Life Insurance Building, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Businesses - Arcade, undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Businesses - Draughon's Practical Business College, undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Businesses - Evening Star, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Businesses - Greyhound, undated (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Businesses - Realty Title Insurance Co. Inc., undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Businesses - Smith, F.G. Piano Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Businesses - Southern Railway, undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Businesses - Taylor's Drugstore, undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Businesses - Towles Studio, Photographer, undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Businesses - Velatis, undated (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Businesses - Washington, Baltimore and Annapolis Electrical Railway Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Businesses - White Cross Milk Co., undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Businesses - Wilson Line Steamer, undated (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Canals - C and O, undated (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Canals - Great Falls, undated (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Capitol - Art, undated (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Capitol - Bronze Doors, undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Capitol - Dome, undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Capitol - East Elevation, undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Capitol - House Chamber, undated (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Capitol - Old Supreme Court Chamber, undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Capitol - President's Room, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Capitol - Senate Chamber, undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Capitol - Statuary Hall, undated (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Capitol - West Elevation, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Cherry Trees, undated (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Churches - Baptist- Calvary, undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Churches - Catholic - Franciscan Monastery, undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Churches - Catholic - Holy Trinity, undated (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Churches - Catholic - National Shrine, undated (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Churches - Catholic - Sacred Heart, undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Churches - Catholic - St. Matthew's, undated (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Churches - Catholic - St. Patrick's, undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Churches - Catholic - St. Stephen Martyr, undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Churches - Christian - National, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Churches - Christian Science - First Church, undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Churches - Christian Science - Fourth Church of Christ, undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Churches - Episcopal - St. Alban's, undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Churches - Episcopal - St John's (Lafayette Square), undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Churches - Episcopal - St. Thomas, undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Churches - Episcopal - Washington Cathedral - Exterior, undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Churches - Episcopal - Washington Cathedral - Grounds, undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Churches - Episcopal - Washington Cathedral - Interior, undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Churches - Lutheran - First Trinity, undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Churches - Lutheran - Georgetown, undated (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Churches - Lutheran - Luther Place Memorial, undated (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Churches - Methodist - Foundry, undated (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Churches - Methodist - Metropolitan, undated (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Churches - Methodist - Mount Vernon, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Churches - Mormon (Church of Jesus Christ of Latter Day Saints), undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Churches - Presbyterian - Central, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Churches - Presbyterian - Church of the Covenant, undated (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Churches - Presbyterian - First, undated (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Churches - Presbyterian - New York Avenue, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Churches - Presbyterian - Sixth, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Churches - Unitarian - All Souls, undated (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Churches - United Church of Christ - First Congregational, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Churches - United Church of Christ - Graced Reformed, undated (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Circles - Dupont, undated (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Circles - Thomas, undated (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - City Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Colleges and Universities - American, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Colleges and Universities - Catholic, undated (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Colleges and Universities - Georgetown, undated (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Colleges and Universities - Howard, undated (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Colleges and Universities - Trinity, undated (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Colleges and Universities - War College, undated (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Commerce, Dept. of., undated (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Constitution Hall, undated (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Continental Memorial Hall - Exterior, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Continental Memorial Hall - Interior, undated (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - District Building, undated (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Embassies - China, undated (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Embassies - Germany, undated (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Embassies - Great Britain, undated (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Embassies - Japan, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Embassies - Russia, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Engraving and Printing, Bureau of, undated (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Events - Bonus Expeditionary Force, 1932, undated (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Events - Misc., undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Exhibits - Santa Maria on Washington Waterfront, Maine Ave., and M St., SW, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Federal Reserve, undated (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Federal Trade Commission, undated (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Federal Triangle, undated (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Folger Shakespeare Library - Exterior, undated (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Folger Shakespeare Library - Interior, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Food Administration Building, U.S., undated (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Fountains - Bartholdi, undated (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Fountains - Capitol Plaza, undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Fountains - Columbus, undated (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Fountains - Court of Neptune (Library of Congress), undated (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Georgetown, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Government Printing Office (GPO), undated (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - "Greetings From Washington", undated (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Hospitals – Walter Reed, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Hotels - Annapolis, undated (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Hotels - Great Falls (MD side), undated (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Hotels - Hamilton, undated (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Hotels - Madison, undated (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Hotels - Quality Inn (Pentagon City), undated (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Hotels - Shoreham, undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Hotels - Washington, undated (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - House Office Building – Exterior, undated (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Houses -, undated (Box 2, Folder 70)
  - Houses - Dolly Madison, undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
  - Houses - Dumbarton Oaks (Georgetown), undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
  - Houses - Girl Scouts "Little House" (1750 NY Ave.), undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
  - Houses - Key Mansion (Georgetown), undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
  - Houses - "Little White House" (21 Madison Pl., NW, Congressional Union Headquarters, undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
  - Houses - Mount Vernon, undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
  - Houses - Octagon, undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
  - Houses - Old Stone (Georgetown), undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
  - Houses - Petersen (House Where Lincoln Died), undated (Box 2, Folder 79)
  - Houses - Rhode Island Ave. (Scott Statue in Background; 1700 Block, North Side of R.I. Ave.?), undated (Box 2, Folder 80)
  - Houses - White House -, undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
  - Houses - White House - Blue Room, undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Houses - White House - Corridor, undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
  - Houses - White House - East Elevation, undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Houses - White House - East Room, undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Houses - White House - Green Room, undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
  - Houses - White House - Lobby, undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Houses - White House - North Elevation, undated (Box 2, Folder 88)
  - Houses - White House - President's Dining Room, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Houses - White House - President's Office, undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Houses - White House - President's Telephone/Telegraph Bureau, undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Houses - White House - Red Room, undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Houses - White House - South Elevation, undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Houses - White House - State Dining Room, undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Houses - White House - Treaty Room, undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Houses - White House - West Elevation, undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Houses - Wilson, Woodrow, undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Inaugurations - Warren G. Harding, 1921 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Inaugurations - Abraham Lincoln, 1891 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Inaugurations - William McKinley, 1901 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Inaugurations - Franklin D. Roosevelt, 1933 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Inaugurations - Theodore Roosevelt, 1905 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Inaugurations - William Howard Taft, 1909 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Inaugurations - Woodrow Wilson, 1913 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Inaugurations - Woodrow Wilson, 1913 or 1917 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Inaugurations - Unknown, 1913 or 1917 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Interior, Dept. of, undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Internal Revenue, Bureau of, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Justice, Dept. of, undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Labor, Dept. of, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Library of Congress -, undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Library of Congress - Annex (Adams Building), undated (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Library of Congress - Exterior, undated (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Library of Congress - Interior -, undated (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Exhibits, undated (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Misc., undated (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Minerva, undated (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Achilles, undated (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Adonis, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Bellerophon, undated (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Boy of Winandar, undated (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Cairn, undated (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Clio, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Comus, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Endymion, undated (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Ganymede, undated (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Hieroglyphics, undated (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - History, undated (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Jason, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Labor, undated (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Law, undated (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Lyric Poetry, undated (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Manuscript, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Melpomene, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Oral Tradition, undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Orpheus, undated (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Paris, undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Perseus, undated (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Pictograph, undated (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Printing Press, undated (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Prometheus, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Religion, undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Mosaics - Seasons, undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Reading Room, undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Second Floor Central Hall, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Library of Congress - Interior - Stairway, undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Library - Public - Carnegie, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Library - Public - Martin Luther King, Jr. Memorial, undated (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Mall, undated (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Markets – Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Masonic Temple, undated (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Memorials -, undated (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Memorials - Barry, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Memorials - Columbus, Christopher, undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Memorials - Ericsson, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Memorials - Farrugut, David G., undated (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Memorials - Founders (Daughters of the American Revolution), undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Memorials - Frederick the Great, undated (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Memorials - Garfield, James A., undated (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Memorials - Gibbons, James Cardinal, undated (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Memorials - Grant, Ulysses S., undated (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Memorials - Greene, Nathanael, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Memorials - Grief, undated (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Memorials - Hahnemann, Dr. Samuel, undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Memorials - Hamilton, Alexander, undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Memorials - Hancock, John, undated (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Memorials - Jackson, Andrew, undated (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Memorials - Jefferson, Thomas, undated (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Memorials - Joan of Arc, undated (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Memorials - Jones, John Paul, undated (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Memorials - Kosciuszko Thaddeus, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Memorials - Lafayette, Marquis Gilbert de, undated (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham - Exterior, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham - Interior, undated (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Memorials - Lincoln, Abraham - Misc., undated (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Memorials - Logan, John A., undated (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Memorials - Marine Corps War Memorial (Iwo Jima), undated (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Memorials - McClellan, George B., undated (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Memorials - McPherson, James B., undated (Box 3, Folder 92)
  - Memorials - Payne, John Howard, undated (Box 3, Folder 93)
  - Memorials - Peace, undated (Box 3, Folder 94)
  - Memorials - Pike, Albert, undated (Box 3, Folder 95)
  - Memorials - Pulaski, Casimir, undated (Box 3, Folder 96)
  - Memorials - Rochambeau, Comte Jean de, undated (Box 3, Folder 97)
  - Memorials - Scott, Winfield, undated (Box 3, Folder 98)
  - Memorials - Sherman, William Tecumseh, undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
  - Memorials - Thomas, George H., undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
  - Memorials - Washington, George (Monument) - Misc., undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
  - Memorials - Webster, Daniel, undated (Box 3, Folder 102)
  - National Geographic, undated (Box 3, Folder 103)
  - Naval Observatory, U.S., undated (Box 3, Folder 104)
  - Navy Yard, U.S., undated (Box 3, Folder 105)
  - Neighborhoods - Chevy Chase, undated (Box 3, Folder 106)
  - Neighborhoods - Cleveland Park, undated (Box 3, Folder 107)
  - Neighborhoods - NE (Corcoran's Hill), undated (Box 3, Folder 108)
  - Organizations - American Association of University Women (AAUW), undated (Box 3, Folder 109)
  - Organizations - Famous Womens' Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 110)
  - Organizations - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
  - Organizations - Masonic and Eastern Star Home, undated (Box 3, Folder 112)
  - Organizations - Methodist Building, undated (Box 3, Folder 113)
  - Organizations - National Housing Center, undated (Box 3, Folder 114)
  - Organizations - National Press Club, undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
  - Organizations - National Society Daughters of the American Revolution, undated (Box 3, Folder 116)
  - Organizations - YMCA, undated (Box 3, Folder 117)
  - Organizations - YWCA, undated (Box 3, Folder 118)
  - Pan-American Union - Exterior, undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Pan-American Union - Interior, undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Parades – Preparedness, June 14 1916 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Parks - Potomac, undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Parks - Rock Creek, undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Patent Office, undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Pension Building - Exterior, undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Pension Building - Interior, undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Pentagon, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Post Office - City - 12th and Pa. Ave., undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Post Office - City - N. Capitol and Mass. Ave., undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Post Office Dept. – 12th and Pa. Ave., undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Potomac River, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Presidents, U.S. - Johnson, Lyndon B., undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Presidents, U.S. - Kennedy, John F., undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Presidents, U.S. - Lincoln, Abraham, undated (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Public Health Service Building, U.S., undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Restaurants - Also Café, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Restaurants - Alex Stuart's, undated (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Restaurants - Alfio's la Trattoria, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Restaurants - Allies' Inn, undated (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Restaurants - Balalaika, undated (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Restaurants - Blackie's House of Beef, undated (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Restaurants - Blue Mirror, undated (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Restaurants - Bonat French-American Café, undated (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Restaurants - Café Burgundy, undated (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Restaurants - Cannon's, undated (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Restaurants - Casino Royal, undated (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Restaurants - Cathay, undated (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Restaurants - China Doll, undated (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Restaurants - Chinese Lantern, undated (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Restaurants - Colony Lounge, undated (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Restaurants - Crown, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Restaurants - Duke Zeibert's, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Restaurants - Flagship, undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Restaurants - France's, undated (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Restaurants - Golden Parrot, undated (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Restaurants - Good Earth, undated (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Restaurants - Gung Ho, undated (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Restaurants - Gusti's, undated (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Restaurants - Hall's, undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Restaurants - Hammel's, undated (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Restaurants - Harvey's, undated (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Restaurants - Herzog's, undated (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Restaurants - Hogate's, undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Restaurants - Hot Shoppes, undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Restaurants - Linda, undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Restaurants - Mayfair, undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Restaurants - Napoleon's, undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Restaurants - Naylor's, undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Restaurants - New Smorgasbord, undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Restaurants - O'Donnell's, undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Restaurants - Old New Orleans, undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Restaurants - Olmstead, undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Restaurants - Pierre, undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Restaurants - Purple Tree Lounge, undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Restaurants - Reeves Coffe Shop, undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Restaurants - Restaurant 823, undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Restaurants - Restaurant Longchamps, undated (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Restaurants - Restaurant Madrillon, undated (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Restaurants - Rib Room, undated (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Restaurants - Roma, undated (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Restaurants - Ruby Foo's Den, undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Restaurants - Schneider's, undated (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Restaurants - Seafare Restaurant and Lounge, undated (Box 4, Folder 65)